<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Examples on Hugo wodpress</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/examples/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Examples on Hugo wodpress</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-au</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/examples/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Example 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/examples/example-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/examples/example-2/</guid>
      <description>Home Referencing Quoting When you are researching a topic, sometimes you want to include the exact words of another author or speaker in your own work. Using someone’s words in their original form is called quoting, or including a direct quote.&#xA;When to quote Quoting is the way to include the exact words of others in our own work. You might want to use a quote when the specific words that an author or speaker has used are important, such as when someone offers a new definition for a term or presents a new theory.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Example 3</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/examples/example-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/examples/example-3/</guid>
      <description>Home Assessments Getting started with assignments Develop your search strategy Choose valid sources Integrating ideas with reporting words Not all information is created equal.&#xA;When you choose information for your assignments, there should be a continual evaluation process occurring. Evaluate information for its relevance and usefulness to your work, and its quality.&#xA;Not all information that is published is credible and reliable, especially if you find that information on the web.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
